techcrates.com 2018-08-28

# Privacy Policy | Technology Review

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## _Use of technical cookies_

This site uses cookies to function well and to provide a state of the art personalized user experience. Third party cookies can be used by our indirect Internet partners like Google, Facebook and Co who have the best technical standards and user privacy settings.

## _Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie_

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network **privacy policy** at the following url **http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html**

Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Tech Crates has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## _Collection of Personal Information_

When visiting Tech Crates, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## _Links to third party Websites_

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## _Changes to this Privacy Statement_

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the _privacy policy_ of Tech Crates then you may contact us using the contact form

Last updated Tue, 21 May 2016
